<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://intercode.interactiveliterature.org/blog</id>
    <title>Intercode Blog</title>
    <updated>2020-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://intercode.interactiveliterature.org/blog"/>
    <subtitle>Intercode Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://intercode.interactiveliterature.org/img/neilSquare.png</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Email forwarding]]></title>
        <id>/2020/03/15/email-forwarding</id>
        <link href="https://intercode.interactiveliterature.org/blog/2020/03/15/email-forwarding"/>
        <updated>2020-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intercode can now forward emails recieved by a convention domain to appropriate staff members. For example, if your convention is hosted at 2020.example.com, and you have a staff position called Webmaster whose contact email is set as webmaster@2020.example.com, Intercode can now automatically forward emails received at that address to all the people in that staff position.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Intercode can now forward emails recieved by a convention domain to appropriate staff members. For example, if your convention is hosted at 2020.example.com, and you have a staff position called Webmaster whose contact email is set as <a href="mailto:webmaster@2020.example.com">webmaster@2020.example.com</a>, Intercode can now automatically forward emails received at that address to all the people in that staff position.</p><p>Additionally, staff positions can now have CC addresses (which will also receive email sent to that staff position) and aliases (additional email addresses that can be used to contact that staff position).</p><p>In order to take advantage of this feature, conventions will need to set the MX record on their domain name appropriately. If you&#x27;d like to do this, please contact us at <a href="mailto:hosting@neilhosting.net">hosting@neilhosting.net</a> for instructions!</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Nat Budin</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/nbudin</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Notifications]]></title>
        <id>/2020/01/27/sms-notifications</id>
        <link href="https://intercode.interactiveliterature.org/blog/2020/01/27/sms-notifications"/>
        <updated>2020-01-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intercode is now able to send SMS (text message) notifications! For conventions that keep online event signups open during the con itself, Intercode will deliver notifications of signups, withdrawals, and waitlist pulls starting 24 hours before the start of the convention. The text of notifications is customizable via the "Notification templates" feature in the Admin section.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Intercode is now able to send SMS (text message) notifications! For conventions that keep online event signups open during the con itself, Intercode will deliver notifications of signups, withdrawals, and waitlist pulls starting 24 hours before the start of the convention. The text of notifications is customizable via the &quot;Notification templates&quot; feature in the Admin section.</p><p>Users can opt out of SMS notifications via a new setting in their user profile for a convention. Texts will come from 415-NEIL-010 (415-634-5010).</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Nat Budin</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/nbudin</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Intercode Schedule Design]]></title>
        <id>/2019/10/03/new-intercode-schedule-design</id>
        <link href="https://intercode.interactiveliterature.org/blog/2019/10/03/new-intercode-schedule-design"/>
        <updated>2019-10-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're rolling out some changes to how the schedule and run buckets display in Intercode 2. Here’s the highlights:]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We&#x27;re rolling out some changes to how the schedule and run buckets display in Intercode 2. Here’s the highlights:</p><h2>Schedule</h2><ul><li>Instead of having a thin green bar that empties as people sign up for an event, the event will have rounded ends, and act as a progress bar that goes up as people sign up. Once the event is full, it will be lightened to show that it is full.</li><li>Events that have unlimited slots will remain rectangular, and have a gradient background to show that you can sign up for them.</li><li>Events that have no slots (i.e. consuite) will remain rectangular, and have a solid background.</li><li>The &quot;you are signed up for this game&quot; has changed to a user/head icon instead of the checkbox that looked like an interactive element.</li><li>The concom only &quot;Schedule With Counts&quot; view has been updated to show the percentage of signups in the same style, as a background progress bar on each event.</li><li>The sorting of events on the schedule has been updated to better group multiple runs of events together if they’re sequential.</li></ul><h3>Schedule Legend Example</h3><p><img src="news_20191003_legend.png" alt="The new schedule legend view, showing examples of types of event"/></p><h2>Signup Buckets</h2><ul><li>Instead of having a broken line that turns from colored segments to gray, we’re displaying a set of empty circles that get replaced by the same user/head icon that we use on the schedule as people sign up. This should be easier to read at a glance.</li><li>When you click on a run in the schedule view, the same set of circles/heads are displayed there as well.</li></ul><h3>Signup Bucket Examples</h3><p><img src="news_20191003_run.png" alt="The view of an event run from its event page, showing the lines of empty circles for open slots"/></p><p><img src="news_20191003_popup.png" alt="The view of an event run from the schedule grid, showing the reorganized popup view with lines of empty circles"/></p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Marleigh Norton</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/marleighnorton</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Nat Budin</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/nbudin</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Kapell</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/dkapell</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>